KARL **GENTNER**

QA ENGINEER

gentnerkarl@gmail.com



kgentner.github.io



(206) 499-5011



Seattle, WA

linkedin.com/in/karlgentner

SKILLS

UIPATH

AUTOMATION HUB ORCHESTRATOR TEST MANAGER STUDIO PRO PIPELINE INTEGRATION

TESTING

SELENIUM CODED UI **AXE ACCESSIBILITY** SAUCE LABS ALM QUALITY CENTER

DEVELOPMENT

.NET CORE MVC **JAVASCRIPT** HTML5 CSS3 MS SQL

OTHER

GIT AZURE DEVOPS VISUAL STUDIO CODE **POSTMAN** MS POWER-AUTOMATE

SUMMARY

QA Engineer with experience in test automation and software development for internal business groups. Versatile and enthusiastic team member with strong communication skills, a passion for learning new technologies, and the curiosity required for complex testing and technical investigation. Currently focused on leveraging UiPath platform for test automation and RPA.

PROJECTS

EPIC UI AUTOMATION

AUTOMATION DEVELOPER

- · Redeveloped existing Epic Ui Automation program with UiPath Platform, enabling automated testing of Providence's electronic medical record system over Citrix.
- Developed custom framework and libraries to enable rapid expansion of additional enhancements.
- Resulting processes reduce manual effort by hundreds of hours for each testing wave.

Technologies: UiPath Studio, UiPath Orchestrator, UiPath Citrix Extension, Excel

LABOR SWEEP TEST AUTOMATION

AUTOMATION DEVELOPER

- Developed automated project and timecard creation for downstream integration testing of Providence's Oracle Genesis ERP migration.
- Reduced manual testing by 85%, increasing test quality for high-impact labor capitalization process.

Technologies: UiPath Studio, UiPath Orchestrator, SharePoint, Excel

MIRA INSURANCE REFERENCE APPLICATION

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Designed and developed a web application to help the Providence healthcare staff of clinics and hospitals accurately register patient insurance.
- Managed time efficiently to ensure punctual delivery for testing and production roll-out dates.

Technologies: .NET Core MVC, Entity Framework, Razor, Bootstrap, and MS SQL

EMPLOYMENT

Quality Engineer - Renton, WA

▶ Software Developer - Seattle, WA

QA Analyst - Renton, WA

Acoustical Consultant - Seattle, WA • BRC Acoustics / Pressure Wave

Recording Engineer - Atlanta, GA

• Providence St. Joseph Health

Self-employed

Providence Health & Services

R!OT Atlanta / Sync Sound

• 03.2019 - Present

• 04.2017 - 02.2019

05.2015 - 03.2017

• 11.2006 - 10.2014

• 04.1998 - 08.2005

EDUCATION

Code Fellows - Seattle, WA

Rensselaer Polytechnic - Troy, NY

Florida State University - Tallahassee, FL • BA: American Studies

• CERT: Full-Stack JavaScript

MS: Architectural Acoustics

10.2014 - 12.2014 08.2005 - 12.2006

• 08.1991 - 12.1995

CERTIFICATION

ISTQB Foundation Level Certification

• CTFL Certified Tester

• 03.2016